Standards, enough!
My guy, Mr. Handsome.
Hey, we have some research to get to.
We're getting to the bottom of this right now.
What do you think a female is looking for
on a guy, on their body?
I would say a six pack,
but I feel like that's not the answer.
Right? I feel like legs are the answer.
You think so?
Do you think the females want the legs?
Why? Why do they want the legs?
****** baby, they like to-
They like to get the drive going?
What is going down here, baby?
They want to feel. They want to feel.
Hell yeah.
Now the next important question.
Are you a, let's say, cherry or melon or a peach guy?
I mean, Justin Bieber just came out peaches.
I like a little bit of both.
What if one is like, voluptuous?
I'm fine if a girl has no pectoral muscles.
She just does skip chest X.
But a little bit of both.
Is there a necessity for you?
Blonde hair, tattoos, it is.
Okay.