They call for you.
The general, he became a slave.
The slave who became a gladied.
The gladied of the defied emperor.
Striking story.
Now that people want to know how the story ends,
only a famous death will do.
What could be more glorious than to challenge the emperor himself in the greater arena?
You fight me.
Why not?
Do you think I'm afraid?
I think you've been afraid all your life.
I might not be invincible.
Who knows no fear?
Your man or one said death smiles at the ball.
All the man can do a smile back.
No wonder.
Did your friend smile at his own death?
You must know.
You were your father.
You loved my father, I know.
But so did I.
That makes us tough, doesn't it?
Smile for me now, brother.
The gods have spared you.
Don't you understand?